how many times have you seen those black
men on the esur boxes you don't know
their names no it it could be latravious
it could be
latravious you know it could it could be
Levant yeah we should find them and give
them their flowers this
month
sh
it so funky
welcome y'all we about to have a fun
time I know we've had a lot of like kind
of intense and serious episodes here at
small doses podcast back to back and
that is um sometimes just the way it is
right that's just kind of like the
Rhythm and the time we're in uh I know
that I've talked about just how like I'm
in like a very depressive intensive
space these days and so it's natural
that that the conversations would kind
of like be reflective of that
nonetheless I am very conscious of the
fact that we all need our pockets of joy
and today I'm giving you a cargo pants
level of pockets of Joy okay we're
taking it back to the cargo pants of the
90s when folks was definitely walking
around looking like hamsters with nuts
in their cheeks but at their knee level
okay it's it's full of joy because we
have corporate Aaron and the the uh the
Brilliance of corporate Aaron as an
existing iCal character the reason why
we wanted to do this is because I know
so many people have experienced this
Character Corporate Aaron created by
Lisa Beasley and said that they both
love her and hate her and I am in the
same boat because she really represents
everything that we know about corporate
and like what it is to be in this
corporate space and it's like you're
watching her and simultaneously
triggered by it but also Affirmed
because by her doing this character in a
satirical fashion she is letting you
know you not crazy they sound like this
they be saying this they be acting like
this they be wanting you to do this and
all of that comes through in this
interview and I need y'all to know this
is the longest she's ever been in this
character you're going to be hearing me
and you're like is Amanda in character I
kind of had to just give in because if I
don't then just is like me shooting her
down and now it's no longer like a a
it's it's no longer an actual exchange
it just is me interviewing um Marian
Williamson again so I didn't want to
give you that and I had to do mind power
control because I had to think what does
Amanda want Lisa to have corporate Aaron
give to the world in these questions and
I hope that we
uh did that successfully because I hope
you have just as good a Time listening
to this as we had recording this and
when I say a good time I want to also
point out anytime you hear radio silence
it's because we're breaking
character because we are cracking up and
we got to get back into the
conversation and um as two black women
who have had to deal with corporate
bullshit in a myriad of spaces you know
particularly in the artistic space at
present you know it it was
really it was really just dope
connecting with Lisa and getting to do
this and it felt very for
me fulfilling because I've been missing
this part of my work like the the the
performer part of my work and it's not
that I miss acting in shows because I
don't want to go back to that corporate
space if y'all think that it's not
corporate at HBO and at NBC Etc all
these places are corporations that have
a studio it's not a studio with a
corporation running it does that make
sense does it make sense AJ does it make
sense yes ma'am it makes sense okay it
makes sense so therefore here we are I
give to you this new episode of small
doses podcast side effects of corporate
featuring corporate
Aaron
enjoy it is a water cooler of
deliciousness
welcome thank
you we're so happy to have you here at
uh small doses podcast you know this is
a topic
that I really have never really broed
breached broed broed um
because I feel like corporate for me has
always been so like just Out Of Reach
you know just like Out Of Reach and when
I came across you and your commentary
and your lived
experience um I said this is somebody
who can connect the dots for us right uh
when I did my comedy special IB KN I had
a joke in there that was less of even a
joke as much as it was just a point of
Rel like relatability where I spoke
about um the proliferation of white
women adding people to emails that don't
need to be added right the the the the
Confluence of the
CC and when I saw you uh in your space
speaking about you know the the
existence of corporate I said this is
somebody who does that this is somebody
who does that but is not a white woman
and so I just became so curious and you
are somebody that I feel like is very um
rooted in the corporate lifestyle so
welcome to the show and I guess my first
question would be
um Erin how did
you find corporate to be the home for
you well that's a great question thank
you so much for having me on I'm a big
fan I saw the special ab noan and I I I
will say there was some critical
feedback that I had just for that part
right there okay concerning the CCE okay
sometimes it is kind of necessary don't
you love it when you look at an email
and you can scroll down and see all
those lines going across to so how many
people reped and you can just keep
scrolling and scrolling and can don't
you love just being in the think of a
thread it feels a bit overwhelming for
me but I can see how some people would
feel that that's like it's home you know
it's like they're being encased right it
looks like sandbags like being stacked
on top of you yeah because sometimes the
line turns from black to purple and I
think that's really
cool I do I do think that that is a
spectrum um that some people do exist on
yeah now you ask how did I find corporat
yeah be or how did or better yet how you
know how did corporate find you right
because I feel like it's a calling yeah
I I definitely think it's a calling it
was also kind of instilled in me ever
since I was little so I legally cannot
talk about my parents but I can talk
about you know as much as I can but our
home is kind of pretty much structured
similar to a company um family dinners
similar to like a boardroom meeting and
so the way I talk is kind of like the
normal way of talking which is why I'm
teaching more people to talk like me and
there was always just kind of like a
path laid out for me and I said this is
a great path I'm going to circle back
and follow up on it so it says do all of
your school go to college when you're in
college network and then your family can
help you establish a career and then
when you establish your career you can
kind of stay there and kind of work
within the system to kind of keep Rising
above in your career yeah yeah yeah yeah
so when you
um got into the corporate space what is
it about it that you feel
like
serves
productivity that's a very interesting
question while you have depending on how
large the company is there's a lot of
moving parts so if all of the parts are
moving the way that they're supposed to
be moving then that means we're driving
the business forward so when I think of
pivotal key players and I think of
people who drive the business forward
you have these different departments
kind of all working with each other and
there's so many initiatives going on at
once that's kind of like peak level
productivity where you're not just
working on one thing you're working on
so many different things you almost
don't even know what you're working on
so there's emails that's happen
throughout the days there's a laning
that has to happen there in there's
procurement teams there's there's
procurement teams for certain
departments you know so if a department
needs something well who are they going
to communicate to there's something in
the system for that and there are people
that carry that out so the whole thing
is kind of like one big old productive
machine do you feel like there's
elements of that machine that are
hampering
productivity I think it's when
individuals don't want to adhere to to
what the machine needs so if you think
about just like any other machine take
your car it needs oil it needs gasoline
it needs brake fluid and need breaks but
let's say if you wake up one morning and
say hey you know what I could bring I
could bring the breakes to the car today
but I'm not feeling it I'm going to take
a day off I'm going to take a mental
health day and I'm going to put the
brakes on everything well that kind of
can stall the situation and before you
know it people are driving the business
maybe too forward and you were there to
say hey is anybody going to have ey
balls on this if we don't have you there
because you're normally pumping the
brakes well then that's going to kind of
slog up the machine kind of thing so I
think people can disrupt the system not
allowing that machine to work
properly what about people in management
can they ever disrupt the system well
naturally we are disruptors okay
so you know just by very nature of us
kind of you know being in this pivotal
role of disrupt what it means to say hey
who's over here doing this who's over
here doing this we've kind of made
overse cool again because nobody wants
to be in the possession of like I
oversee people but it's very necessary
so we can make sure we see everything
that's going on to make sure all of
these moving Parts because if you're in
this department you may not have any
kind of purview into what's going on
over here so it's it's going to take
somebody to say hey I just pinked so and
so they know that this is going on or
glad I'm here to kind of help mitigate
any kind of future
issues well it's interesting that you
say oversee because one of the key tools
for the overseers during slavery was a
whip um but you guys aren't allowed to
use whips now so what would you say is
the new like
proverbial
getting it back getting it
back what would you
say what would you say is the new
proverbial whip that is used by Manager
overseers overseeing Management
incorporate of our new era okay in in a
Neo in a neoc colonialist era yeah and I
can definitely understand kind of the
layering and mapping of historical
contact of like how we got to this
moment but I do want to be clear there
are no there are no slaves that work for
me here okay so I just kind of want to
make sure legal told me to say hi we
don't have slaves here we do pay
people we did kind of Boral from that
overseer model because it kind of works
for corporate okay and it's kind of the
only model we've kind of been following
in America and so even right down to the
way that we kind of like do our
spreadsheets and keep Tops on you know
different employees and documents
that system was developed then and we
just kind of added some to it so there
are some benefits to you know what
slavery has has given they they've given
America the management system that we
have so I'm glad we got rid of the whole
like actual slaves being slave I'm glad
we started to pay people but you know
the role of the manager has kind of
always been kind of very pivotal to
making sure that the mission is being
driven forward so when I think of like
what C the proverbial wh be well you
know now there are a lot of you know
measures put in place so we don't
physically make people do the work
exactly we're not chaining anybody to a
desk you know that's your choice if you
want to because some people do that to
kind of build in a discipline measure
yeah yeah yeah and you know I think some
people think well okay how am I being
punished if I am not doing the work well
you might look at it like maybe it's a
performance plan that kind of whip you
into action or or maybe it's you know in
your performance reviews it's kind of
like the proverbial did you are you so
yeah yeah I could say maybe that's
probably kind of one of the layering
ways um
probations anything like that anything
that kind of leads up to a termination
possibly of um so those those type of of
measures I can say anything that kind of
puts the employee back into the mind
frame of oh we got to we got to perform
yeah so
yeah you know I mean it's it's really
profound when you said that um slavery
actually gave us the management system
here in America you know if it if it
ain't broke don't try to emancipate it
you know you know I mean you know
there's a lot of bad history out there
and it's just kind of good that we can
kind of turn it around and use it in a
positive way well I feel like that's
something that um corporate really tries
to instill in folks right like how to
all always see the Silver Lining how to
make the lemons into lemonade um what
are ways in which you work with your
employees to manage negative or
difficult situations and and turn them
into positive well you know the first
thing is to always approach always
approach work with an extrovert mindset
okay show that you're very happy to be
there okay smile can you give me right
can you give me an example so for
example if you're hopping on to a
meeting let's say this is your seventh
meeting of the day and everybody in the
meeting that's already there you've also
been in meetings with them all day right
so when you pop onto that seventh call
we kind of kind of take it for granted
that we've seen these people all day and
we just kind of hop on the call and say
okay guys here okay so that's been a
long day right no no you always want to
pop on and say hey everybody good
afternoon I'm so happy to be here let me
introduce myself and then we can go
around the room every call that I'm on
we always intr ourselves even if we just
got off of a CL all together oh wow
yeah but that enthusiasm is it's so it
really plants the seed it keeps you
connected I remember when I went on
Safari in Kenya on the Masai Mara and
after
day
yeah so so I remember when
I I remember
wait Lisa I don't even I love you and I
don't even know you I just want you to
be clear I love you
tooa don't feel like we already know
each other like well yes yes yes you are
bringing joy to me that I have been
lacking for weeks and I want you to know
that
um I ventured on a group trip to Kenya
uh the masara the lands of the masara
people and again I was on a group trip
right so it's me it's 15 other
individuals 15 other personalities okay
and we're in the trucks and we're
Trucking along on the path and we're
seeing the antalope we're seeing the
gazel we're seeing the zebra and then
you can see lions and bear well there's
no bears in Kenya but you're seeing
elephants Etc but by day two the group
said H more zebras more analou more
gazel and it just made me think about
what you're saying about the zooms
because it's like no we're coming back
into the zoom with the animals and the
gazel and the and the zebras and they
are going to be just as happy to see us
today as they were yesterday and we need
to greet them with the same enthusiasm
exactly I'm going to take that anecdote
P of reframe it kind of map it on as my
own and begin to use that in front of my
calls cuz your it's just Wildlife as
real life that's all it is wild life is
real life that's a t-shark you know what
we could actually I would I will
actually when I come and speak at the
conference for for the company that you
work for what's the name of it again the
company well we're MC management
mcmanager
legistics so uh I was asked to come do a
diversity uh Dei program for I recommend
it y thank you so much um and so I've
put together some notes and you know I
can't wait to come out there and just
really talk to them about just like
diversity diversion uh divertisment and
you know B DDD yeah yeah yeah and just
the ways in which um we can you know
diversity Equity inclusion everything
right not just people um how do we
diverse the equity inclusion dogs right
how do we bring dogs into the workplace
how do we how do we bring dogs in the
work more dogs in the workplace you know
they they how do we bring cats cats per
at a at a megahertz for healing how does
that help us in what we're doing in
terms of this working on an initiative
this is breaking up a tree to to use a
dog analogy I had an initiative there
was some people that saying they were
stressed at home and I said well come
into the office but if I tell them that
cats are in there and that cats are
healing they can get their healing at
the out so take your mental health day
at work yeah
yeah revolutionary yeah revolutionary
really truly innovating the
workspace what are ways so I I'm sorry I
cut you off with my uh my anecdote in
the motherland so you were saying that
there are ways in which you feel like
people can uh bring positivity into the
workplace or you know change a negative
to a positive and one of the first
things you said was about enthusiasm do
you have any others that you can give us
because I know there's people listening
they're incorporate and are finding
themselves having to really show up yeah
yeah yeah you gota you gotta show up you
got to show up if it's about getting up
earlier whatever you need to do to show
up and be your best selves now here's
the thing a lot of people there's this
term in the industry of diversity and
inclusion when you know it was really
kind of popular RIS in 2020 and
companies made a lot of promises one of
the phrases was bring your whole self to
work best self to work now what you're
going to have to realize is the company
has a version that is defined as best or
whole yeah yeah so you have to be in
line with that so for example okay for
example Lisa Beasley was telling me a
story of how she said hey this company
said I can show up as my whole self so
she would show up to these pivotal work
meetings with like smoking a blunt in
her mouth and we said well that's that's
that's not your best self and she said
well it
it is so like who's to say well the
company the company can tell you who
your best self is so if you want to know
who your best or whes self is think
about what company you're at see what
they want your best in whol self to be
and map that on to
yourself that that really feels like
um that feels difficult to
do yeah but I feel like if you're really
if you're really someone who cares about
the company then you'll do it regardless
yeah it's really all about the company
missions the company Mission and values
and everything should be lading up to
that when we talk about company missions
and values um what is the company
Mission and value of uh make management
management management well we are
certainly we have our mission kind of in
the hands of a third party Black
copywriter to kind of help us our
mission right now so I can tell you that
our Old Mission was just to fulfill the
mission of the company with values and
goals okay yeah okay okay yeah it's
really great to have like a nice tight
sentence maybe one to three sentences
and you want to kind of try to stay away
from anything specific and the more you
can use the word mission in the mission
statement the better staying away from
anything specific it sounds like our
constitution oh they were they were
specific about the right to bear arms
they were they were specific about every
but what black people should be given
I've actually been thinking about the
Constitution a lot lately interesting
tell me more yeah I just thought that it
was interesting that here we have this
chance to kind of build this pivotal
document and write out the gate the
first few things or we can have guns and
say whatever we want I think that's very
interesting for a company structure
someone who loves structure if that's
kind of like the basis of the foundation
I just think that's very interesting I
didn't see the word mission in there so
you know I I think it's the priorities
of the Constitution I think do need to
be looked at yeah I think well you know
you said it best when you said of the
company because this is a company it's
not really a country um and so you as
somebody who is so just Adept at
understanding company structures it's
fascinating that you see something wrong
with that because you know what the hell
you're talking about yeah I do yeah I do
I think those I think maybe I should
kind of work on maybe rewriting the
Constitution to can't fit a company
structure since that is what it is a lot
of people don't know that America is a
business yeah and we as constituents are
kind of more so employees of this
business because if we don't do our part
the business kind of tinks and when the
business tinks we go all over the world
kind of searching for some help to kind
of put us back on track so it's kind of
similar to when a company is going under
they go to their friends and say hey do
you have a billion dollars I can borrow
do you have a billion I can borrow and
sometimes your friend doesn't have a
billion dollars you can borrow so you
take
it taking it I mean I'm curious um as a
black woman
working as a black woman
work I just like to side note that in
high school Andrea Schwarz would
actually do that for real at Dr Phillips
high school she literally would do that
with black people and Brazilians and
literally one time was like oh my God I
went to Universal and there were so many
Brazilians that I couldn't even believe
it and I was like did you just blank out
Brazilians
Brazilian
well um so as a black woman in corporate
where do you feel like you are an asset
um in a unique way that maybe your hawi
counterparts are are not well you know
there's more spaces that I can be in
that they can't be in so that makes me
an asset to the company and it kind of
also allows me to kind of open up and
speak to other groups I think the most
fun part is I still kind of hold the
missions and values of the company down
to a te similar to the people who were
in my position perform me regardless of
color so you know it's not that I'm
perpetuating anything but I like to
think that if I stick true to the
structure there's no surprises and the
company can still be moving forward but
this time if you have kind of like a
block pivotal partner there you know I
can I can maybe get some more like black
eyeballs on things in the office I can
kind of go to like you know the other
women of the office and raw Ross a
spoonball over there you know I can kind
of use my identity to kind of occupy
certain spes to fulfill the
mission you know I wonder um about
certain situations had someone like you
been in the room what would you do so
I'd love to just run some some some
scenarios by you to hear kind of like
what your expertise would have added to
that that was lacking oh
absolutely um so when Walmart decided to
create products for
juneth and they said we're going to make
an ice cream for juneth that is a
Kool-Aid fried chicken waffle
flavor
um had you been in the room when this
was
ideated uh where where do you feel like
you would have added or taken away from
that type of uh thinking yeah now I do
have a clarifying question was this one
flavor rolled into one or were these
three different Flav okay okay so that's
kind of interesting I would have been
there kind of pivotal voice to say hey
you said Kool-Aid Fried Chicken and
watermelon what no that actually seems
like it would be more logical but it was
waffles oh waffles okay chicken and
waffles and Kool-Aid yeah okay that's
just okay I would have been there to
kind of speak to the flavor profile okay
so in those meetings sometimes the the
there's push back from the community the
consumers that said hey who is in that
room and often there is not someone that
looks like me in that room exactly so
the expectation is that someone in in
like me would come to the room if I were
there and say hey just don't do this at
all this is a Miss but with this one I
see an opportunity okay oh tell me more
okay yeah you got to think about the the
flavor profile of that so when I eat
chicken and waffles it's accompanied by
syrup sometimes yeah and then I often
don't drink another sweet beverage
following that because when you do two
sweet things on your mouth it kind of
cancels it out so that's just not a
smart flavor profile that they were
putting forward okay so I would have
done a more conducive constructive meal
that kind of automatically all goes
together so it would have made sense and
most of the Kool-Aid if it if it wasn't
clarified if it was red or grape which I
also like to pinpoint out that one is a
color one is a flavor but we still
acknowledge them as two different things
yes you know I think to be that pivotal
voice in the room is important still get
the initiative out to the black people
for the you know black people die yeah
but stay true to the tenants of what
that culture would actually really want
regardless if they want it or not
sometimes they don't know that they want
Kool-Aid and chicken flavored things Al
together sometimes company has to tell
them that and sometimes that imagination
does come from you know our our right
counterparts and that's just them trying
to you know try try you know what and I
guess who are we who are we to to stop
them from trying yeah you know yeah yeah
I would encourage people to say hey
where is the money going to that you're
making all these products for or is
there an initiative within the company
that the funds are is it just going all
up to the same kind of wealthy person
there as Sam getting it
all got you I got another one for you
yeah so um Vogue magazine which we do
know is a company um they recently uh
published um a piece that that credited
football player Travis Kelce with the
fade haircut yeah um and so this is
another situation where I said you know
what there wasn't an Aaron theopolis in
the room actually can you just tell me
thopas is such a unique name is it Greek
no so actually I I'm sorry I cannot
legally talk about my parents and that
would expose them but I will say that my
great great great grandfather he used to
throw up a lot and a lot of my past when
I was younger I didn't like working and
anytime I wanted to work I would throw
up okay yeah so for a long period of
time work made me want to throw
up interesting so it's kind of like how
like there's people whose last name is
Milner because they were milers um you
know your last name is theopolis because
y'all were throw uping a lot yes
ha yeah look at I mean just the
histories and etymologies of our
genealogies right just yeah just hurling
so much Rich culture yeah yeah just
hurling pun intended through history
through history yeah so what would you
have said had you been lanyard it up
yeah in the room when that editor um
said to the corporate you know
at that conference table this is going
to be my piece that I'm going to
contribute to this month's fogue
magazine uh Travis Kelsey as the creator
of the fade what would have been like a
corporate um um acceptable way for the
black person in the room to say you're
out of your mind okay well I don't know
if I would have said it that way but
what I would have done is I would have
came into the room and I would have said
hey everybody I would have looked every
in the eyes thank you guys so much for
being a pivotal partner my name is
Corporate eron I'm the manager for the
manager logistics for management
management and if just kind wants to
kind of call us all in to kind of think
about the critical ways in which we're
kind of approaching the situation okay
and then I would give everybody time in
the room to go around and say what they
did in exhaust and that's so those
people can feel their voice fill the
room so they can know they feel like
they're a part of the conversation by
just entering and saying hey what do you
do here you are important okay we do
value you yeah okay then I would have
gotten down to the critical information
I would have said I would have looked
around and said I noticed that of all of
the men here the identities are kind of
not representative of kind of this
cultural experience dealing with the
fade here now a lot of people didn't
grow up and you know some people have
Super Cuts as their kind of based
knowledge of Fantastic Sams yeah and you
know I teach a lot of hair workshops at
our company because you know yeah I've
getting I get called in a lot on my hair
and I say hey is nice to talk about
people's hair yeah this is mayal hair so
of course I have to have to I have to
have to like you know speak up for
myself and say hey everybody's hair is
different but we do kind of have to
honor the cultural influences and give
proper credit so that I do know so when
it came to that particular Travis issue
what I would say is hey let's include
him and maybe for other white people who
have also pioneered the fade and then
that way we can show there's kind of
like a big group of people all coming
together to say hey ha doesn't belong to
any one person we're all coming together
and say hey we wear the F now what I
would say is I would encourage any
members of the company and a black ERG
to kind of use that moment to speak up
and said hey yeah we are kind of like
the cultural um creators of this
movement that dates back here here here
and what I find interesting is I would
ask that they bring some numbers to the
table maybe some pivotal pictures maybe
some snapshots throughout history to
kind of prove Kid and Play yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah I saw house party I
was there so kind of like showing like
hey there were origins of this it's
interesting though with this one in
particular I think this is maybe not the
first time for sure but one of the first
times we're seeing this happen to black
men in our culture so I think that's
very interesting to see them kind of
saying what I've been rcking the fade so
and you know because we seen it before
with Kim K's signature braid or you know
things like that Haley Baldwin with the
clean the clean look with a bun and and
hoop earrings yeah it's it's a very it's
very interesting Dynamic so I would be
in there in the room to provide some
pivotal pictures some timelines some
snapshots I would create a deck for sure
to prove got have a
this was already a thing I think I would
pull in some images I remember going to
the barber shop when I was little with
my dad that I can't talk about and they
would have these pictures and these
numbers and you would order a number
haircut yes and so no no one there were
no names it was just the number yes so I
think one if we want to kind of prop up
Travis for this phenomenal hair moment
well well we might need to consider just
adding him to one of those charts and
giving him a number
I want to get the number seven and it's
Travis
Kelsey I think he's 44 oh interesting
okay yeah make make I actually hate that
I know that that's true inclusion if we
make the haircut a number but when we
single him out and give him a name you
know I mean how many times have you seen
those black men on the esur boxes you
don't know their names no it it could be
latravious it could be
latravious you know it could it could be
Levant yeah we should find them and give
them their flowers this
month
I I want to talk
about just and I want this to be a safe
space for you okay um
what was your experience like when you
learned that juneth would be coming to
the
office
well honestly I will okay thank you for
the safe space this is kind of very
vulnerable for me to talk about anytime
a wave of emotions came through me
number one being oh no people are going
to want this day off a because before it
came to the office as a hard launch
holiday it was was just kind of
lingering around I said it it was a
thing for for the blacks yeah yeah you
know I was kind of one of those people
that said oh okay I understand the
origins of it there were some people
somewhere who hadn't got the message and
some people may sure that they got the
message and I said I get it but I was
kind of in that critical first batch who
knew so I kind of celebrate the regular
day you know so you know I understand I
understand I haven't mapped back my
Origins to the people that didn't know
yet so I can't claim
know understand the camarad nature
around it I get it no fun if the homie
can't have some I get it I'm down
so when I met you last night baby before
you opened up your
Gap I had respect for you lady yeah but
now I take it all back
yeah yeah
because well you gave me all
your you
even leave your number on the
cabinet and I
promise I will give you a for my
previous email call doesn't that sound
like freedom in
America yeah so I get it so I was a
little nervous I said know what's coming
they're going to want the day off and so
now I'm kind of in this batttle I'm so
glad I can be vulnerable here I'm kind
of in this bottle where it's like well
hey we have to open this up to everybody
now if this is a national holiday yeah
okay yeah yeah I don't know what are
some initiatives that you've done in the
office to open it up for everybody well
number one visuals I don't think that
maybe black people should be the only
one on the visuals for juneth get
everybody on there because juneth is a
country it's our it's our whole entire
country's issue so if we could just have
everybody represented in that branding
yeah everybody everybody because even if
you think about it even the owners yeah
t yeah everybody even the slave owners
had a pivotal role because if those
slave owners hadn't have kept it from
them there wouldn't have been no J so we
kind of have to kind of so family
portrait yeah we got to kind of circle
back to those families I said we're GNA
keep this on the low and we do they wear
the costume of the slave owner than in
the picture just to
differentiate just so we're clear on
roles well we do have some dress up time
in the office we do kind of do some
reenactments um there are no cameras
allowed for those because we don't want
our company to get cancelled but it is
just kind of a vulnerable time for
people to kind of stay true to history
and you can kind of come with whatever
inspires yall okay okay have you ever
considered um an altar building an altar
in the office to the formerly enslaved
just as just as a way an exercise of
atonement I haven't I haven't tell me
more give me more suggestions maybe we
should have an agenda in meeting about
this and kind of build this initiative
out well I've heard some um I've heard
some members of the uh formerly uh
enslaver
Community um
yeah speak
to them being um haunted on
juneth oh by the former enslaved of
their enslaver line and and then what
what the problem though is that now when
they come to work on June 19th they're
completely uh in ineffective right
because they're reeling from the
Poltergeist of right they're reeling
from the Poltergeist of of Lucy and
Willie who slid down the banister the
night before and now they're here in the
office they're unkempt they're unfocused
and now we've lost a day of productivity
because of a day of um negro toity right
yeah you know what I am going to rush
this alra initiative because one it'll
bring people back into the office there
you go and two any chance we can get to
Kana collect some of those spirits and
you know hey if we collect kind of like
some old slave Spirits they it might
Foster an environment for more work to
happen in the office there you go yeah
because
that and I'm not saying that we implore
the slave module oh no not at all I
would never I would never but this
brings us to a Full Circle moment which
was that we discussed earlier about how
the actual original um company policy of
um you know really just working people
with literally complete abandon and
keeping tabs actually set up America for
the company efficacy that it continues
to uh operate under so it really is a
full circle it's a full circle moment
and who better to actually get insight
from than those who actually were there
right exactly exactly exactly I'm
picking up what you're putting down I'm
picking up what you're putting down I'd
love to hear your thoughts on and I know
this is a dirty word so I you know we
ready we we do hear at small doses we
have talked to Chris Smalls who is the
uh head of the Amazon labor union and
um I would love to hear from you
about unions and where you feel they fit
into the landscape that you are in
personally I have two answers one the
one I know that I'm supposed to say
which is I support unions I support
people coming together to speak on
behalf of people now the second thing
that I want to say is there's a lot of
things you have to think about when
starting a union okay you're essentially
starting another structure so are you
ready to kind of take on this extra
pivotal workload when you us that energy
for your actual job so sometimes a
question like hey is you being a part of
this Union taking away from your job
responsibilities there's a lot of
organizing that you have to do there's a
lot of outside meetings you're not paid
for this sometimes there's union dues
and people can kind of think of a
structure to compensate their top
leaders but it all gets like a lot of
messy about the idea of having a
representative or a representation for
people in the workplace to kind of go to
the company you know I like to think we
have an open door where you can just
come in and say hey here are some issues
that I'm having I don't see why you have
to gather 5,000 can we actually role
play that yeah yeah sure sure okay okay
um actually your door would be open
actually your door would be open your
door would be open you're you feel like
that type of manager so I'm knocking but
it's I'm knocking on an Open Door you
guys I'm knocking on an Open Door
yeah hey
doors open come on in it's so good to
see you good morning
hi hi um so I just wanted to do a quick
touch base uh
because I have been feeling a bit under
served at the company and it's really
starting to feel like a union would be
the next step but I wanted to come and
talk to you first okay I'm just going to
stop you right here I know we're role
playing but I'm going you some pivotal
NS okay if you can use some more core
language like drilling down poor
competencies and kind of give yourself
kind of like a compliment sandwich what
are you doing for the company and then
the meat is going to be like but I think
that's and then have another piece of
breath that's like but you're doing
great okay
so back open the door come on
in hey corporate
Aaron um so I just wanted to First say
that I'm really
thriving um in a in a number of specific
areas within the structure of our
company nice um there are some places
that have been giving me pause okay that
are causing me to consider the the
necessity for a union oh
okay I did really enjoy our company
picnic and the Sumo costume
that you all got after watching that
episode of The Office where Pam realized
that she was in love with Jim and then
um Jim realized that he was in love with
Pam and also we also learned at that
time that um Angela was actually having
a a relationship with Dwight in a very
real way so I know that that episode was
the inspiration for this moment and that
made me feel good as somebody who did
love the office and I even appreciated
the British one as well yeah great great
thank you so much I heard a lot of good
things on there nice to hear that you're
thriving in specific areas so I heard
you say that um now in terms of kind of
like this Union structure have you
spoken with like a direct report is this
the first time am I the first point of
contact for this big the big you
word yes I wanted to come to you first
because I know how important you are to
the company and I know how clearly you
understand the mission and the upward
directives of the latter yeah and I'm on
your side but I do have to ask a couple
of pivotal questions just in case I need
to chase it up to leadership okay are
there people that are joining you in on
this initiative do you kind of already
have a core group start
at I'm not sure that I feel comfortable
um answering that question as much as it
seems like your next question is going
to be
who okay well I like to see that you're
thinking ahead that's why we have you
here okay you always are a great
forecaster okay so I'm not going to say
you know I don't need to know who okay
okay but I mean if you do kind of want
to Anon anonymously send me an email and
kind of let me know that'll be great but
I don't I don't have to I don't have to
know who and I don't want to discourage
you from starting a union but just
understand that unions can kind of take
away from the company on the public side
they can kind of affect kind of business
in a different way that some people
don't understand it can affect the
stocks it can affect public opinion of a
company and it kind of puts you know
think of it we're like a family here
right think of it like with your family
sometimes you don't want everybody
knowing your family's business so
sometimes you just put you know your
uncle in the back room and close the
door and we have company say don't go
back there okay but we're working on it
when company leaves we let Uncle out and
we say okay get back out here Uncle
let's let's let's continue working on
some things so that's kind of one of the
reasons we just kind of want to keep as
much as can kind of hear where we can
all work on a together leadership and
the employee base working together if
the employees are working without
leadership I don't see how any
initiatives or any coms or anything are
going to be successful because you have
to fed your union into our strategic
Communications plan so we have a very
lofty way that we communicate here from
the SE Suite to the management to our
senior leadership team to the board so
it's going to take some time to these
initiatives forward so you have to kind
of keep that in mind you got some good
administrative chops to kind of up a
union
here well I learn from the best okay
from you now what I will say is that if
you do go forward with this Union can
you not tell them that I encouraged you
in any way and that you know our
relationship is just professional as a
pertains to the work and I'm very happy
to kind of lead you and Mentor you and
pertains to the work but anything
outside of that I will ask that we just
kind of keep it kind of not outside up
here okay but keep me but we are a
family and I love you so keep me post he
me okay yeah and scen um okay thank you
so and I feel like our listeners really
will resonate with that you know because
so much of that was um just
representational of the ways in which
the corporate structure attempts to talk
without really actually
talking and yeah yeah yeah but it's a
it's a skill set that some of us don't
have but that when you do have it really
allows you um to move without really
moving um you know it's it's it's
interesting I've heard I've heard that
before and I guess if I if I do kind of
consider it and take the analysis of it
I think there was a lot of movement in
that conversation even though we kind of
end it back I think I just pinged it
back to you you have some pival
decisions to make now but I can
definitely understand how you know some
people have said something about like
defensiveness or there was just some
other words that I didn't understand
double Advocate or just kind of like I
don't know turning it back to the I
don't know I I get a little confused
yeah sometimes I get a little confused
by it the way I guess people are getting
confused by me so we're all confused so
we have that in common so for everybody
that's confused by me I am also confused
confused it's a
confused
Community speaking of community um my
patreon community definitely has
questions for you and so we're going to
head on over to the seal
Squad my husband bu kind of these
excursions where I can work while I'm
there so you know sometimes you kind of
take advantage of this work home
structure and so like hey if I could do
the same thing in Italy for a couple of
weeks then why
not live it up girl
yeah once you've already addressed it
and HR gas lights you that means HR the
r now stands for racist and instead of
it being for human resources it actually
stands for hella racist hella racist
okay that's new I haven't heard that
before
okay I think of Consciousness I think of
like planets and stars and so when I
think of like human when I think of
humans at work I think of like you're
performing a role you just do that job
but if you like care about Humanity then
pick a company that cares about
Humanity well corporate Aaron I really
appreciate you taking time out today to
talk with us I know that you have a lot
of initiatives that you are pushing
through throughout the day and so I hope
that we have not derailed any of your
goals for today um but is there anything
that you would like to leave our
audience with any words of
wisdom um any uh you know uh
inspirational posters that you hang on
your desk like is there anything that
you want to give us to carry us through
my fa to be the lanyard that we hang
from yeah thank you so much for having
me on I think it's very important that
we have these pivotal one-on-one
conversations having to sit down and
talk about everything at a very high
level yes I want people to kind of
reframe what it means to Circle back
follow up and close the lo I want people
to understand what does it mean for you
what are some things that you need to
Circle back to what are some things that
you need to follow up on and what are
some things that you need to close the
loop on yeah now sometimes these phrases
just aren't All About Us corporate
people if you find yourself if you're
not in a corporate world at all there's
still the need to kind of circle back
you know some people need to Circle back
to some dreams some people need to
follow up on the next stop of
accomplishing something and some people
need to close the loop on some
relationships so I would say that that
is my lyard that I would kind of want to
leave there you all have it um you can
check out more corporate Aaron at
corporate Aaron and so many other places
uh none of which are the office and
there you have it I hope that was just
as much fun for y'all as it was for us
remember to Circle back follow up and
close the loop all right per my previous
email are y'all enjoying the
conversation oh I know you are that's
why I need you to Circle back follow up
and close a loop on watching it on
patreon